《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead."
不敢相信他会带我们的东西跑掉
I can't believe he would just take our stuff and go.
他显然不想被找到
He obviously doesn't wanna be found.
他想的
Yes, he does.
我们来此请求你与我们一同反抗救世军
We came to ask you to join us in fighting the Saviors.
会死很多人  不仅是救世军
People will die, and not just the Saviors.
我可以为友人达里尔提供庇护
I offer our friend Daryl asylum.
他在这里很安全
He will be safe here.
是时候反抗了
It's time to fight.
不
No...
我不想参与这事
this is something I am not a part of.
加文  让你的人住手
Gavin, tell your man to stop.
黛安
Diane.
好的
Got it.
好箭法
Good shot.
我妹妹有过一条那样的裙子
My sister had that dress.
别想了
Don't think about it.
很好
Nice.
越来越有条不紊了
It's getting to be like clockwork.
现在吗  头儿
Now, boss?
是的  杰瑞
Yes, Jerry.
看上去少了
It looks light.
也许你该再看看  加文
Perhaps you might look again, Gavin.
我们履行了义务
We've met our obligations.
没错
You're right.
看上去不怎么多  但  八  九  十
Doesn't seem like much, but 8, 9, 10.
你说得对
You're right.
我想要他的枪
I want his gun.
实际上  我觉得就不该给这混蛋配枪
In fact, I don't think this asshole should have a gun ever.
坏小子不许碰枪
No guns for bad boys.
是你先打的我  混球
You hit me first, prick.
你说什么
What's that?
好了
Okay.
这下该如何是好
Where do we go from here?
是啊  陛下
That's right, Your Majesty.
这下该如何是好
Where do we go from here?
把武器给他  理查德
Hand him your weapon, Richard.
放下枪  白痴
Stand down, idiot.
去死吧  你个孙子
Suck on it, you little shit.
理查德
Richard! ?
住手
Stand down!
以西结  你知道我不能容忍这种事
Ezekiel, you know I can't have this.
是我们不能容忍这种事
We can't have this.
理查德将被禁止参与我们未来的会面
Richard will refrain from attending our future exchanges.
不不  以西结  你得一直把他带上
No. No, Ezekiel, you're gonna keep bringing him.
因为假如这种事继续发生
'Cause if this doesn't stop,
假如这发展成了一个真正的问题
if this starts becoming a real problem,
你还记得我说过什么吧
you remember what I said.
他会是第一个被球棒砸的
He is still batting first on the lineup.
我自己刚刚差点都动手了
Almost did it myself just now.
我知道这不是他的错  但...
I know it's not his fault, but...
不能再发生这种事了
this has got to stop.
所以...
So...
也许以后得...
things might need to get a little...
野蛮点
visceral.
杰瑞德  快他妈起来
Jared, get the hell up!
我们走吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
我能不能...
Can I, um...
我能不能要回我的棍子  麻烦了
Can I have my stick back, please?
这是别人给我的
Someone gave it to me.
这人已经去世了
Someone who's gone.
加文  你得让我把这个傻逼揍一顿
Gavin, you got to let me turn up this dipshit.
不  不行
No! No!
你...
Just...
看下气氛好吗  大师
read the goddamn room, sensei.
走吧
Let's go.
m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻译     Reginamoon CS小明漫画家 小酸奶
翻译     凉粉 蘑菇 小僵僵 送小孩
校对     送小孩
时间轴     加森  涛涛
后期     送小哥  拉图
是啊
Yeah.
总监     送小孩
我妹妹可爱那条裙子了
My sister loved that dress.
你今天使棍很灵敏啊
You were quick with that today.
令我刮目相看  本杰明
Impressive, Benjamin.
告诉过你  我进步了
Told you I'm getting better.
进步得有点太快了
You were a trifle too quick.
知道如何打架
Just because you now know how to fight
不意味着你应该去找茬
doesn't mean you should seek one.
发生得太快  我来不及考虑
Yeah, but it just happened. I wasn't thinking.
你必须考虑
You have to.
从现在开始  你都要考虑
Every time from this time forward, so you shall.
好吗
Yes?
好
Yes.
理查德
Richard.
稍后我们得谈谈
We shall speak later.
杰瑞
Jerry.
你棍子使得真霸气  伙计
You're sick with this stick, man.
杰瑞
Jerry!
你要去医务室吗
Hey, uh, do you want to head to the infirmary?
不  我没事
No. I'm okay.
你们坐卡车去哪了
Where'd you go in them trucks?
我得跟达里尔单独谈谈  好吗
I need to speak to Daryl alone. That okay?
我帮你找点东西包扎伤口
Yeah, I'll get you something for that cut.
好
Yeah.
你们去见救世军了  对吧
You went to see them, right?
对
Yeah.
协议的一部分吗
Part of your deal?
你没毛病吧
What the hell's wrong with you?
你流血了
You're bleeding.
他们打的
They did that to you.
-你知道他们是什么东西  -我知道
- You know what they are. - I do.
知道吗  如果卡萝尔在这
You know, if Carol were here,
如果她看到了
she saw all that...
如果她知道了亚伯拉罕
if she knew about Abraham...
和格伦的事
and Glenn...
她会带我们去找他们
she'd be leading us right to them,
干掉他们所有人
ready to kill them all.
没错
She would.
这也是她离开的原因
And that's why she left, man.
我在练习
I'm practicing.
得多用弓箭了
Gonna have to start using these more.
救世军深知不该让我带枪在他们附近晃悠
The Saviors are smart enough to know I shouldn't have a gun around them.
摩根说你是弩手
Morgan said you're a bowman.
为什么
Why?
因为我们的目标一致
'Cause we want the same things.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
行尸走肉
『第七季  第十集』
我们需要一些事来打动以西结
We need something to move Ezekiel.
此区域禁止野营
现在就是机会
This is it.
亚历山大  山顶寨和神之国先下手为强
Alexandria, the Hilltop, and the Kingdom hitting first,
重创他们  然后从世上抹杀救世军
hitting hard, and then we wipe the Saviors from the Earth.
保护人们
Keeping people...
很多很多好人
dozens and dozens and dozens of good people...
保护他们
keeping them safe.
公墓
他们从这条路走
They ride this road.
有车路过  肯定是救世军
If we see cars, it's the Saviors.
最近他们三五人一伙常来
They've been coming in packs of two or three lately.
所以我需要你
That's why I need you.
我一个人对付不了
I can't take them alone.
先用枪攻击他们
We're gonna hit them with the guns first...
然后用燃烧瓶
and then the Molotovs.
然后再用枪  直到他们全灭
Then back to the guns until they're dead.
-为什么用火  -要看起来惨烈点
- Why the fire? - Needs to look bad.
发现尸骸的救世军
The Saviors who discover what's left...
我们要让他们震怒
we want them to be angry.
我留了踪迹到我做的伪武器库
I left a trail from here to the weapons cache I planted,
到以西结在乎的某人住的小屋
to the cabin of that someone Ezekiel cares about.
谁啊
Who's that?
不过是他遇见的某个独行者
It's just some loner he met.
有时候他会送食物过去
Sometimes he brings food.
他们为什么不住在神之国
Why don't they live in the Kingdom?
我不知道
I don't know.
她住在外面  会死在外面的
She lives out there, she'll die out there.
是个女人吗
It's a woman?
这有什么关系  她比我们胆子还大
What does that matter? She's got more balls than you and me.
反正她都要死的
She's gonna die either way.
救世军来了发现他们的人死了以后
When the Saviors come and find their buddies dead,
如果他们不蠢
if they know their elbow from their asshole
会追踪明显的踪迹
and can follow an obvious spoor,
他们就会找到武器库  然后是小屋
they're gonna go to the weapons cache and then to the cabin,
他们会攻击这个女人
and they're gonna attack this woman.
她叫什么
What's her name?
也许他们会杀了她  也许杀不了
Maybe they kill her, maybe they don't,
但这会让以西结知道该做什么
but it's gonna show Ezekiel what he needs to do.
她名字  叫什么
Her name. What is it?
她很强  也许她能活下来
She's tough. Maybe she'll live.
他妈的说名字
Say her damn name!
卡萝尔
Carol.
我真希望你不认识她
I hoped you didn't know her,
但我不知道你会在意
but I didn't think you'd care,
因为你知道必须做什么
'cause you know what needs to happen.
-不行  -也许她能活的
- No. - ?Maybe she'll live.
听着  这就是我们的机会
Look, this -- this is how -- this is how this could happen.
这就是除掉救世军的方法
This is how we can get rid of the Saviors,
这样我们都有未来
how we all can have a future.
她独自住在野外
She's living out there on her own,
-只是在等死  -不行
- just waiting to die. - ?No!
如果我们不做什么  会死更多的人
If we don't do anything, a hell of a lot more people are gonna die,
想活的人
people who want to live!
你给我离卡萝尔远点  听见了吗
You stay the hell away from Carol, you hear me?
他们来了
It's them.
我们可以等着事情变糟
Look, we can wait for things to go bad,
失去人们
we lose people...
或者我们可以咬牙做难事
or we can do the hard thing...
选择自己的命运
and choose our fate for ourselves.
不行
No.
对不起
Sorry.
会有更多人的
There'll be more.
或者那些人
Or those --
过会儿会再从这条路回去
they're gonna ride back this way later.
我们还有机会
We'll have another chance.
但时间不多了
But we're running out of time.
如果你和你的人想反抗救世军
If you and your people want to move against the Saviors...
就得尽快下手  你们需要神之国
you need to do it soon, and you need the Kingdom.
我们要做的事总会有牺牲的
What we have to do requires sacrifice one way or another.
我们这样的人
Guys like us...
已经失去了太多
we've already lost so much.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
我知道...
I know...
卡萝尔  孤身在外生活...
that Carol, living on her own like that...
她现在可能已经死了
she might as well be dead right now.
如果她受伤  她死了
She gets hurt, she dies,
她染上风寒
if she catches a fever,
她被行尸杀了...
if she's taken out by a walker...
她被闪电劈中...
if she gets hit by lightning --
只要她出了一点点事  我就杀了你
anything -- anything happens to her, I'll kill you.
我愿意为神之国而死
I would die for the Kingdom.
那你怎么不去死
Why don't you?
你们有没有领头的人
Are you a collective, or does one lead?
这位
This.
我叫瑞克
I'm Rick.
你们的命在我们手里
We own your lives.
想换回去吗
You want buy them back?
你们有什么好东西吗
Have anything?
你们抓了一个我们的人
Well, you have one of my people.
加百利
Gabriel.
我想先见见他  然后再谈
I want to see him first. Then we can talk.
你们拿走的船上的东西被别人夺走了
The boat things you took got taken.
我们看到了  就拿走了剩下的东西
Saw them, so we took the rest.
顺便把他也带了回来
And we took him.
那你就知道我们没有可以用来
Well, then you know we have nothing
交换我们性命的东西
to buy back our lives with.
你们也即将一无所有
That's what you'll have soon -- nothing.
因为我和我的人听命于
Because me and my people already belong to that group
那伙夺走船上物资的人
who took those supplies from the boat.
他们叫救世军
They're called the Saviors.
我们的命在他们手里
They own our lives.
如果你们杀了我们
And if you kill us,
就等于夺走了他们的东西
you'll be taking something from them.
他们会来找你们
And they will come looking.
遇上救世军  你只有两个选择
You only have two options when it comes to the Saviors --
被杀或者被他们所支配
either they kill you or they own you.
不过有一个出路
But there is a way out.
加入我们
Join us.
加入我们  反抗他们
Join us in fighting them.
不
No.
罗西塔  不要
Rosita, don't!
所有人都住手
Everybody, stop!
等等
Just wait!
放了我们  否则我杀了她
Let us go, or I will kill her!
立刻放了塔米尔
Away from Tamiel now.
救世军  他们...
The Saviors, they --
他们还有其他地方  其他社区
they have other places, other communities.
他们有各种东西
They have things --
食物  武器  车  燃料
food, weapons, vehicles, fuel.
你们想要什么  救世军都有
Whatever you want, the Saviors have it.
放了塔米尔
Away from Tamiel.
你说吧
Your words now.
如果加入我们  一起打倒他们
If you join us and we beat them together,
你们可以获得很多他们的东西
you can have much of what's theirs.
与我们一起战斗  你们少不了好处
Fighting with us, you'll be rewarded,
多到超乎你们的想象
more than you can imagine.
我现在就要
Want something now.
瑞克
Rick...
他无所不能
can do anything.
这群人
This group?
他们来这里找到了我  离家那么远
They found me -- here, so far from our home.
你想要什么
What do you need?
告诉我们  我们会帮你弄来的
Just tell us -- we'll get it for you.
我们会向你们展现出我们的实力
We'll show you what we can do.
就现在
Now.
塔米尔  布里昂
Tamiel, Brion...
把瑞克带到"坡顶"
show Rick Up Up Up.
没事的
It's okay.
这边
Here.
坐吧
Sit.
谢谢  我没事
Thanks. I'm okay.
这些人是谁
Who are these people?
我猜  是你新交的好朋友吧
New best friends, I guess?
他们要带瑞克去哪
Where are they taking him?
我们所有人  自灾变之后
All of us, here since the change.
只拿  不费心
We take. We don't bother.
但情况变得越来越难
Things grow harder.
有时候我们打开罐头  发现里面已经腐坏了
We open cans, sometimes inside's rotten.
日子一天天过去
Time's passed.
情况又再次变了
Things are changing again.
或许我们也该变了
So maybe we change.
或许吧
Maybe.
我需要知道你是不是认真的
Need to know you're real with this,
看你是否值得
that you're worth it.
你干了什么
What did you do?!
瑞克
Rick!
我没事
I'm all right.
瑞克
Rick!
墙
The walls!
利用墙
Use them!
你现在相信我们了吗
You believe us now?!
告诉我们你想要什么
Just tell us what you want...
我们帮你弄来
and we'll get it.
枪
Guns.
很多
A lot.
很多枪
拿到后我们会加入你的战斗
And then we fight your fight.
你确定我们会赢吗
You know we will win?
我当然确定
Oh, I know it.
结束后  我们要分一半的战利品
After, we get half of what's won.
给你们三分之一
Oh, you'll get a third.
并且把之前从我们这偷的东西还回来
And we're taking back what you just stole from us.
一半
Half.
三分之一
A third.
一半
Half.
三分之一
A third.
三分之一  但不归还我们偷的东西
A third, and we keep what we stole.
我们拿走的罐头  还你们一半
Half of the jars, the ones we took.
这次不还价
One time, this time.
同意吗
Yes?
说同意
Say yes.
同意
Yes.
还有枪
And the guns.
我们在那艘船边上等了很久
Waited by the boat long time.
想要点补偿
Want something for it.
所以就这样
So it's this.
罐头和枪  枪和罐头
Jars and guns, guns and jars.
你们就等着别人替你们从船上拿出物资吗
You waited for someone to get the supplies off that boat for you?
等很久了
Long time.
我们只拿  不费心
We take. We don't bother.
里面那个...
You had that...
那个东西就是为了让别人证明自己的吗
thing down there for someone to prove themselves?
不是
No.
他叫温斯洛
His name was Winslow.
你想对加百利做什么
What were you gonna do with Gabriel?
走吧
Go.
协议是有期限的
Deal expires.
很快过期
Soon.
你叫什么
What's your name?
简迪斯
Jadis.
达成协议了
We have a deal.
我和理查德说了不要再来看我
I told Richard no more visits.
我知道
I am aware.
你渴望独处
Your desire is solitude.
我就是这样下令的
That's what I've ordered to be facilitated.
我的人是来清理行尸的
My men are here clearing the wasted.
行尸向来都不顾他人是否想独处
The dead are quite inconsiderate when it comes to those who are wanting to be alone.
我以为我们轻手轻脚
I thought our efforts would be quiet enough
不会引起你的注意
to fall beneath your notice.
是你打开了门
You're the one who opened the door.
我的警戒线被碰到了
Tripped my wire.
我以为我及时抓住它了呢
Thought I caught it in time.
抱歉
Sorry.
您把它们藏得很好  女士
You hid them well, lady.
不要叫她女士
Don't call her "Lady."
夫人  小姐  太太
Ma'am, Ms., missus...
你可以闭嘴了
You can shut up now.
收到
Copy.
再见  陛下
Goodbye, Your Majesty.
等等
Hold up.
水果馅饼
Cobbler.
凯文说你喜欢吃
Kevin said you like it.
这是以备你开门的
Just in case you did open the door.
走吧
Go.
好了
Okay.
耶稣带我们来了神之国
Jesus took us to the Kingdom.
摩根说你离开了
Morgan said you just left.
我在外面的时候
I was out here.
看到了你
I saw you.
你为什么要走
Why'd you go?
我必须走
I had to.
我站岗的时候听到了动静
I heard something when I was on watch,
是从墙里面传来的
from inside the wall.
我去储藏室查看  有个人偷袭了我
I went into the pantry, one of them jumped me.
她很生气  因为他们等了那么久
She was angry because she didn't get the supplies from the boat
最后也没得到船上的物资
after all the waiting.
所以他们逼我把余下东西装好
So they made me pack up everything else.
但是她说他们在船附近  所以我希望...
But she said they were at the boat, so I hoped...
不  你不只是希望
No. You didn't just hope.
你把我们引到了这里
You got us here.
我已经开始要失去信心了
I was beginning to lose faith.
但是我看到了你
But then I saw you.
然后你向我点头
And you nodded at me.
你知道我没有离开
I mean, just the fact that you knew I didn't leave,
你搜寻后找到我
that you searched and found me,
你看到这么多人
that you, seeing these numbers,
你看起来很...
you seemed so...
高兴
glad.
我们会纠正这一切的
We will set things right.
但是在这以前境况会非常困难
But things are gonna get very hard before that time.
我们必须坚持
We have to hold on.
我会的
I will.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你为什么笑
What made you smile?
什么让你这么自信
What made you so... confident?
有人向我展示了敌人也可以变为朋友
Someone showed me enemies can become friends.
我们不应该回亚历山大
We shouldn't be going back to Alexandria.
我们得留在外面
We need to stay out
为协议找枪
and look for the guns for this deal.
瑞克受伤了  亚伦受伤了
Rick is hurt. Aaron is hurt.
我更担心埃里克看到我的脸
I'm more nervous about what Eric will say
又成这样会怎么说
if he sees my face like this again.
家里的人需要食物
People back home need food.
瑞克想带回补给  然后重整旗鼓
Rick wants to bring supplies back and we regroup,
所以要这样做
so that's what we're doing.
那我自己去
Then I'll go on my own.
我们要待在一起  就这样
We are sticking together, and that's it.
你怎么了
What is your problem?
我们现在不是要挑起争端  罗西塔
We're not looking for a fight right now, Rosita!
我们在为战斗做准备
We're getting ready for one.
战斗时刻都有  塔拉
It's always a fight, Tara.
我不会让任何人挡我们的路或拖后腿
I'm not letting anyone get in our way or slow us down.
阻止别人掠夺我们也好
If we got to stop people from taking from us
从别人那里抢也好
or we got to take from other people,
我不在乎
I don't care.
我们要赢
We win.
成熟点吧
Grow up.
枪
Guns.
快点
Soon.
快点  要么免谈
Soon. Or else.
我们帮你缝好针后
Once we get you stitched up,
我们马上回去找枪  好吗
we'll go right back out and find the guns, right?
好的
That's right.
你知道去哪找吗
Do you have any idea where?
不知道  但是这从没阻止过我们
No, but that's never stopped us before.
塔拉  你在外面比我们走得都远
Tara, you've been out further than any of us.
至少你能告诉我们别去哪找
At least you can tell us where not to look.
好的
Yeah.
当然
Sure thing.
我们走吧
Let's go already.
等等
Hold -- Hold on.
为什么你...
Why are you...? ?
因为我们赢了
Because we won.
代替你失去的那个
And to replace the one you lost.
好了
All right?
我们走
Let's go.
我不能失去任何人
I couldn't lose anyone.
不能失去任何一个
I couldn't lose any of them.
不能失去你
I couldn't lose you.
我杀不了他们
I couldn't kill them.
我可以杀
I could.
我会杀
I would.
如果他们伤害我们的人
If they hurt any of our people --
伤害更多的人  我就会这样做
any more of them -- that's what I would do.
那之后我将不再是以前的我
And there wouldn't be anything left of me after that.
救世军  他们来了吗
The Saviors -- did they come?
是的
Yeah.
有人受伤吗
Did anyone get hurt?
大家还好吗
Is everybody okay?
救世军有没有...
Did the Saviors...
家里的大家还好吗
Is everybody back home okay?
达里尔
Daryl...
他们来了
They came.
我们杀光了他们
We got them all.
跟剩下的敌人达成了协议  就像以西结一样
Made a deal with the rest of them, like Ezekiel.
大家都没事
Everyone's all right.
还吃不吃饭了  我得是个国王
We gonna eat or -- or I got to be a king or something
才能在这吃饭吗
to get food around here?
闭嘴
Shut up.
以西结
Ezekiel...
他人好吗
is he okay?
我觉得挺好的
Yeah, I think he is.
自己保重  好吗
Watch out for yourself, all right?
它对你很温驯
Well, you're good with her.
以西结会印象深刻的
Ezekiel will be impressed.
我想养老虎当宠物的人
Well, figure any guy that has a pet tiger
不会坏到哪去
can't be that bad.
卡萝尔觉得他挺好
He's okay by Carol.
我找到她了  在外面那座小屋子里
Yeah, I found her, out in that little house.
我当时说的话
Look, what I said...
我说她
when I said she just...
离开了
went away...
是她让我说的
it's what she told me to do.
我懂
No, I get it.
我们需要神之国
We need the Kingdom.
你要促成合作
You got to make that happen.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉  但是
I mean, I -- I really am, but, uh...
不能是我
it can't be me.
听着  你所坚持的东西
Look, whatever it is you're holding on to...
早就没了
it's already gone, man.
醒醒吧
Wake the hell up.
你和我一样  达里尔
You're the same as me, Daryl.
你对我毫不了解
You don't know shit about me.
不  我了解
No, I do.
因为你没告诉卡萝尔发生了什么
'Cause you didn't tell Carol what happened.
你没有  不然她会来这里的
You didn't, 'cause she'd be here otherwise.
我对此很高兴
And I'm glad for that.
我们都在坚持着一些东西
See, we're all holding on to something.
我早上回山顶寨
I'm going back to Hilltop in the morning
去做准备
and getting ready.